listimpact.com 2018-11-25

# ListImpact.com | Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how ListImpact.com uses and protects any information that you give ListImpact.com when you use this website.

ListImpact.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

ListImpact may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

**Information Collected**  
In order to use this service a person must register using his or her contact information such as your name and email address. This information is used to login to use our service and to contact the member regarding our service and or products. Upon registration and each login your IP address is recorded. We use this information to provide our services and features to you, to improve those services, and to provide you with customer support.

**Security**  
We take every precaution to protect our members information. Only the administrator of this website has access to members email address and other information. We do NOT sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

**Members right to Cancel**  
All members have a right to cancel their account at any time. A removal link can be found in the members navigation.

**Links to other websites**  
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**  
A member, at any time, may go to their account information and update their information.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions, concerns or comments about our privacy policy you can contact us by our [_HELPDESK HERE_](http://listimpact.com/helpdesk)
